/* Questions and answers for the quiz */

let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: 'Where do Rachel and Ross go on their first date?',
        answer: "Ross's museum",
        options: [
            'The cinema',
            "Ross's museum",
            'Central Perk',
            'The Empire State Building'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 2,
        question: 'Monica organises her towels into several categories. But how many?',
        answer: '11',
        options: [
            '4',
            '6',
            '9',
            '11'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What are Monica and Ross' parents called?",
        answer: 'Jack and Judy',
        options: [
            'Jack and Judy',
            'Jack and Jill',
            'Peter and Margaret',
            'Gerry and Mary'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What's the first thing Ross says at the beginning of the opening episode?",
        answer: '"Hi..."',
        options: [
            '"Has anyone seen my fossil collection?"',
            '"How YOU doin?"',
            '"Could I be wearing any more clothes?"',
            '"Hi..."'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 5,
        question: 'Which character says the last ever line in the series?',
        answer: 'Chandler',
        options: [
            'Gunther',
            'Phoebe',
            'Chandler',
            'Rachel'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 6,
        question: 'How many hours of Friends episodes are there to watch?',
        answer: '90 and a bit',
        options: [
            '73 and a bit',
            '84 and a bit',
            '90 and a bit',
            '112 exactly'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 7,
        question: 'Chandler and Joey had two pets. What were they called?',
        answer: 'Chick Jr. and Duck Jr.',
        options: [
            'Don and Ivana', 
            'Brian and Larry', 
            'Walter and Sergio', 
            'Chick Jr. and Duck Jr.'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What is the name of Joeys acting agent?",
        answer: 'Estelle',
        options: [
            'Andrea',
            'Estelle',
            'Martha',
            'Carole'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 9,
        question: 'What did Ross dress up as to teach Ben about Christmas and Hanukkah?',
        answer: 'The Holiday Armadillo',
        options: [
            'The Holiday Aardvark',
            'The Holiday Armadillo',
            'The Holiday Turtle',
            'The Holiday Tortoise'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 10,
        question: 'Which job did Rachels fianc√© Barry Farber do?',
        answer: 'Orthodontist',
        options: [
            'Lawyer',
            'Plumber',
            'Orthodontist',
            'Journalist'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Chandler and Ross were a band while they were at college. Can you remember the band's name?",
        answer: 'Way, No Way',
        options: [
            'Flock of Birds',
            'Wyld Stallyns',
            'Way, No Way', 
            'Mosh Bros'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 12,
        question: 'Who was the youngest person in the Friends gang?',
        answer: 'Rachel',
        options: [
            'Rachel',
            'Joey',
            'Phoebe',
            'Chandler'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 13,
        question: 'Apart from untidiness, what annoys Monica the most?',
        answer: 'Animals dressed like humans',
        options: [
            'Cheesy garlic bread',
            'Microwave popcorn',
            'Canned soup',
            'Animals dressed like humans'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 14,
        question: 'Ross is allergic to which kind of fruit?',
        answer: 'Kiwi'
        options: [
            'Lemon',
            'Apple',
            'Kiwi',
            'Pomegranate'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 15,
        question: 'Phoebe dated a scientist called David. In which Belarus city did he work?',
        answer: 'Minsk',
        options: [
            'Minsk',
            'Grodno',
            'Mogilev',
            'Pinsk'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "When the Friends gang went to London for Ross' wedding, which member of the Royal Family did they bump into?",
        answer: 'The Duchess of York, Sarah Ferguson',
        options: [
            'Prince Harry',
            'Princess Anne',
            'The Queen',
            'The Duchess of York, Sarah Ferguson'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "Ross had a son called Ben. What was Ben's first word?",
        answer: 'Hi',
        options: [
            'Dinosaur',
            'Coffee',
            'Daddy',
            'Hi'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "Monica dated a millionaire for a while. What was his name?",
        answer: 'Pete Becker',
        options: [
            'Paul Becker',
            'Jake Becker',
            'Pete Becker',
            'Boris Becker'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "Ross had a son called Ben. What was Ben's first word?",
        answer: 'The Duchess of York, Sarah Ferguson',
        options: [
            'Dinosaur',
            'Coffee',
            'Daddy',
            'Hi'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "Phoebe has a twin sister. What's her name?",
        answer: 'Ursula',
        options: [
            'Scarlett',
            'Ursula',
            'Sharon',
            'Rita'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "How many times has Ross been married?",
        answer: 'Three times!',
        options: [
            'Just the once',
            'Twice!',
            'Three times!',
            'Even the actor David Schwimmer has lost count!'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "What was the name of Joey's childhood imaginary friend?",
        answer: 'Maurice',
        options: [
            'Mordecai',
            'Murdoch',
            'Maurice',
            'Monty'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "Which of these is NOT one of the nicknames Rachel's parents call her?",
        answer: 'Creampooft',
        options: [
            'Sweet pea',
            'Pumpkin',
            'Sweetie',
            'Creampooft'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 23,
        question: "How are Friends episode names written?",
        answer: '"The one with___"',
        options: [
            '"The episode that includes____"',
            '"That ____ episode!"',
            '"The one with___"',
            'In hieroglyphics'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 24,
        question: "In which city is Friends set?",
        answer: 'New York City',
        options: [
            'Los Angeles',
            'New York City',
            'Miami',
            'Seattle'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 25,
        question: "Who's worn a turkey on their head?",
        answer: 'Monica',
        options: [
            'Monica',
            'Phoebe',
            'Chandler',
            'Joey'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 26,
        question: "What's the title of the Friends theme song?",
        answer: "I'll Be There For You",
        options: [
            "I'll Be There For Them",
            "I'll Be There For Those",
            "I'll Be There For You",
            "I'll Be There For That"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 27,
        question: "What's the name of the coffee shop used by the characters?",
        answer: 'Central Perk',
        options: [
            "St James' Perk",
            'Central Perk',
            'Froth Of Khan',
            'Daily Grind'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 28,
        question: "What instrument does Phoebe Buffay play?",
        answer: 'Guitar',
        options: [
            'Drums',
            'Guitar',
            'Flute',
            'Synthesiser'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 29,
        question: "What hangs on Monica's purple door?",
        answer: 'A yellow picture frame',
        options: [
            'A key hook',
            'A coat hook',
            'A yellow picture frame',
            'A cap'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 30,
        question: "What is the name of Phoebe's alter-ego?",
        answer: 'Regina Falange',
        options: [
            'Phoebe Neeby',
            'Monica Bing',
            'Regina Falange',
            'Elaine Benes'
        ]
    }

    
]